[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "How would you like to play my ex-husband?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "to", "play", "my", "ex-husband", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What made you get up one day and say I'm going to do this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "you", "get", "up", "one", "day", "and", "say", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CD", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "How bad are you going to miss it, Bill?", "question_tokens": ["How", "bad", "are", "you", "going", "to", "miss", "it", ",", "Bill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "I'm driving a cab at night now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "driving", "a", "cab", "at", "night", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Have you heard from the president since your donation?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "heard", "from", "the", "president", "since", "your", "donation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, no, because it wasn't to him, it was to the super PAC.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "no", ",", "because", "it", "was", "n't", "to", "him", ",", "it", "was", "to", "the", "super", "PAC", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Is it a silly argument?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "silly", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "It's a silly argument.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "silly", "argument", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "That's still hypocrisy, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "still", "hypocrisy", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, first of all, he would just -- he would out-and-out lose this election if he didn't -- it is not hypocrisy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "he", "would", "just", "--", "he", "would", "out-and-out", "lose", "this", "election", "if", "he", "did", "n't", "--", "it", "is", "not", "hypocrisy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Even if you think it's morally and ethically wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "if", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "morally", "and", "ethically", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Of course, because otherwise he doesn't win.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "because", "otherwise", "he", "does", "n't", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "But given that Romney is outspending all his competitors with these super PACs, and like 10-1 and he still isn't getting very far, certainly not winning his election battle at the moment, what makes you think the super PACs are actually that effective?", "question_tokens": ["But", "given", "that", "Romney", "is", "outspending", "all", "his", "competitors", "with", "these", "super", "PACs", ",", "and", "like", "10-1", "and", "he", "still", "is", "n't", "getting", "very", "far", ",", "certainly", "not", "winning", "his", "election", "battle", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "what", "makes", "you", "think", "the", "super", "PACs", "are", "actually", "that", "effective", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well, that's true.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Would every coach do that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "every", "coach", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "You will try to --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "will", "try", "to", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Would every coach do that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "every", "coach", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Of course, every -- they always have.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "every", "--", "they", "always", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "It's true, when Rick -- when Rick Santorum says, you know, Obama thinks that your -- I don't know what -- what did he say about Obama that he wants to rule over you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "true", ",", "when", "Rick", "--", "when", "Rick", "Santorum", "says", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Obama", "thinks", "that", "your", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "--", "what", "did", "he", "say", "about", "Obama", "that", "he", "wants", "to", "rule", "over", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "But here's the problem.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "here", "'s", "the", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick", "Rick Santorum", "Obama", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "How dare you say you won't be taking your orders from the Pope?", "question_tokens": ["How", "dare", "you", "say", "you", "wo", "n't", "be", "taking", "your", "orders", "from", "the", "Pope", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I don't think he read the speech properly because that's not what Kennedy was saying.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "read", "the", "speech", "properly", "because", "that", "'s", "not", "what", "Kennedy", "was", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "What do you think of that whole argument on both sides?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "whole", "argument", "on", "both", "sides", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "It's similar to the silly thing about you -- the designated hitter and how that's a hypocrite.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "similar", "to", "the", "silly", "thing", "about", "you", "--", "the", "designated", "hitter", "and", "how", "that", "'s", "a", "hypocrite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "How much should the government lead, and how much strays into nanny state, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "should", "the", "government", "lead", ",", "and", "how", "much", "strays", "into", "nanny", "state", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Well, sometimes you do need a nanny state.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "sometimes", "you", "do", "need", "a", "nanny", "state", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Did you find that funny or not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "find", "that", "funny", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I hadn't seen that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "n't", "seen", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "What's to get upset about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "to", "get", "upset", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "You -- was it at the \"Vanity Fair\" party you met Tim Tebow?", "question_tokens": ["You", "--", "was", "it", "at", "the", "``", "Vanity", "Fair", "''", "party", "you", "met", "Tim", "Tebow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tim Tebow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Do you like him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Satan, Hitler?", "question_tokens": ["Satan", ",", "Hitler", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "Well, first of all, it's a joke.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "joke", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hitler"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Inspiring?", "question_tokens": ["Inspiring", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 286, "question": "People who are religious?", "question_tokens": ["People", "who", "are", "religious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "If you work from the point of view that most Americans are not atheists like you, then actually, if they do believe in God, having a clean living, superbly talented professional sportsman actually being very, I think, modest, you know, humble --", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "work", "from", "the", "point", "of", "view", "that", "most", "Americans", "are", "not", "atheists", "like", "you", ",", "then", "actually", ",", "if", "they", "do", "believe", "in", "God", ",", "having", "a", "clean", "living", ",", "superbly", "talented", "professional", "sportsman", "actually", "being", "very", ",", "I", "think", ",", "modest", ",", "you", "know", ",", "humble", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Why can't he do it with his religion, if he believes?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "he", "do", "it", "with", "his", "religion", ",", "if", "he", "believes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, he can.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "So?", "question_tokens": ["So", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "ORGAN: And they actually, I suspect, do believe that it's perfectly acceptable for people of religious influence to work in politics as well and govern.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "And", "they", "actually", ",", "I", "suspect", ",", "do", "believe", "that", "it", "'s", "perfectly", "acceptable", "for", "people", "of", "religious", "influence", "to", "work", "in", "politics", "as", "well", "and", "govern", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "If Jeremy Lin came to you and said, look, I want you to join me in prayer and I will score 20 more points against the Lakers, would you do it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Jeremy", "Lin", "came", "to", "you", "and", "said", ",", "look", ",", "I", "want", "you", "to", "join", "me", "in", "prayer", "and", "I", "will", "score", "20", "more", "points", "against", "the", "Lakers", ",", "would", "you", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremy Lin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Maher"]}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Get on your knees and start praying, Bill Maher.", "answer_tokens": ["Get", "on", "your", "knees", "and", "start", "praying", ",", "Bill", "Maher", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "How did you hear the news?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "My wife called me this morning.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "wife", "called", "me", "this", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Were you good friends?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "good", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Well, yes, we were quite good friends.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "we", "were", "quite", "good", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Was he content with his life, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "content", "with", "his", "life", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Oh, I think so, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "so", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to him, Micky?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "you", "spoke", "to", "him", ",", "Micky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "It would have been just a few months ago.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "have", "been", "just", "a", "few", "months", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Micky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Did that bring Davy a lot of pleasure, the fact that you guys were back together and getting great reviews and so on?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "bring", "Davy", "a", "lot", "of", "pleasure", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "guys", "were", "back", "together", "and", "getting", "great", "reviews", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Always did -- did all of us, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Always", "did", "--", "did", "all", "of", "us", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Davy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What do you want me to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "me", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "One of your quick little things.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "your", "quick", "little", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Did he remain proud of his English roots, Micky?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "remain", "proud", "of", "his", "English", "roots", ",", "Micky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Oh, absolutely, he had family back there.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", ",", "he", "had", "family", "back", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Micky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "When you're hearing all the tributes today, Micky, and all the music being played again and so on, what's your abiding memory of Davy Jones?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "hearing", "all", "the", "tributes", "today", ",", "Micky", ",", "and", "all", "the", "music", "being", "played", "again", "and", "so", "on", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "abiding", "memory", "of", "Davy", "Jones", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Oh, boy, it's a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "boy", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Micky", "Davy Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Working.", "answer_tokens": ["Working", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "I'm going to find out the secrets of the most devilish woman on television?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "find", "out", "the", "secrets", "of", "the", "most", "devilish", "woman", "on", "television", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I'm too lucky.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "too", "lucky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "You know, back in Britain, you're not that famous, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "back", "in", "Britain", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "that", "famous", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "That's very true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "very", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "When I won the Emmy -- they didn't, when I was nominated, I wasn't on the list.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "won", "the", "Emmy", "--", "they", "did", "n't", ",", "when", "I", "was", "nominated", ",", "I", "was", "n't", "on", "the", "list", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "But if you don't like him, you don't have to marry him, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "like", "him", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "marry", "him", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "I think there's different ways to describe an arranged marriage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "different", "ways", "to", "describe", "an", "arranged", "marriage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "How did things develop?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "things", "develop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "We just got on.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "just", "got", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "Well, if you let me talk, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "let", "me", "talk", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Does your mom take all the credit?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "your", "mom", "take", "all", "the", "credit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "She just said, I did introduce you and I say, yes, you did.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "just", "said", ",", "I", "did", "introduce", "you", "and", "I", "say", ",", "yes", ",", "you", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Perish the thought?", "question_tokens": ["Perish", "the", "thought", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Oh, God, that would be --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "God", ",", "that", "would", "be", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "To have a little Kalinda?", "question_tokens": ["To", "have", "a", "little", "Kalinda", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "To have a little Kalinda.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "have", "a", "little", "Kalinda", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "But is that -- I mean, how do you feel about becoming 40?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "that", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "becoming", "40", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I know when people say that to me, it doesn't worry me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "when", "people", "say", "that", "to", "me", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "worry", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "What is she like then, Angie?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "she", "like", "then", ",", "Angie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "Very nice woman.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "nice", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Angie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "And brad?", "question_tokens": ["And", "brad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Very nice man.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "nice", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Did you all hang out together?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "all", "hang", "out", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "Occasionally.", "answer_tokens": ["Occasionally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Who rings who?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "rings", "who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Stop being so naughty, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Stop", "being", "so", "naughty", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Do you go out and have a few beers?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "go", "out", "and", "have", "a", "few", "beers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "No, we don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Would I like to be as famous as that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "I", "like", "to", "be", "as", "famous", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "We got a little glimpse of it there, but you put this down to an Indian diet that you had, (INAUDIBLE), right?", "question_tokens": ["We", "got", "a", "little", "glimpse", "of", "it", "there", ",", "but", "you", "put", "this", "down", "to", "an", "Indian", "diet", "that", "you", "had", ",", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "EX", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Did they really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "I'm surprised you didn't discover that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "surprised", "you", "did", "n't", "discover", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "How did that make you feel as a young man?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "as", "a", "young", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "Terrible.", "answer_tokens": ["Terrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "That's awful, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "awful", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Horrible.", "answer_tokens": ["Horrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "How did you react to this critique from your agent?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "react", "to", "this", "critique", "from", "your", "agent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "That maybe that was the reason I wasn't giving the roles because I was fine in delivering the dialogue and that maybe a sign I should work on it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "maybe", "that", "was", "the", "reason", "I", "was", "n't", "giving", "the", "roles", "because", "I", "was", "fine", "in", "delivering", "the", "dialogue", "and", "that", "maybe", "a", "sign", "I", "should", "work", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "So when you now see yourself as this little vamp from \"The Good Wife,\" you must feel pretty good, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "when", "you", "now", "see", "yourself", "as", "this", "little", "vamp", "from", "``", "The", "Good", "Wife", ",", "''", "you", "must", "feel", "pretty", "good", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "It's very strange watching myself on that, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "strange", "watching", "myself", "on", "that", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "What does your husband make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "your", "husband", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "Well, sometimes, every time I have other characters, and I come home with my hair and makeup, he's like, take it off because I hate your make up.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "sometimes", ",", "every", "time", "I", "have", "other", "characters", ",", "and", "I", "come", "home", "with", "my", "hair", "and", "makeup", ",", "he", "'s", "like", ",", "take", "it", "off", "because", "I", "hate", "your", "make", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "How would you like to play my ex-husband?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "like", "to", "play", "my", "ex-husband", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Are you serious?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "serious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "I'll speak to the kings.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "speak", "to", "the", "kings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "Are they negotiable?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "negotiable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "Negotiable.", "answer_tokens": ["Negotiable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 740, "question": "How is Raj going to feel about this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "Raj", "going", "to", "feel", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "Oh, I'm sure -- he's a big fan of yours, I'm sure, he --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "--", "he", "'s", "a", "big", "fan", "of", "yours", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", ",", "he", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]